hoyts.com.au 2014-11-03

# Privacy Policy | HOYTS

In this policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”), “we”, “us” and “our” means The HOYTS Corporation Pty Ltd (ABN 31 006 082 551) and any related body corporates. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it describes the way in which we collect and handle your personal information for the following HOYTS services:

\- HOYTS Cinema;  
\- HOYTS Kiosk;  
\- HOYTS Rewards;  
\- HOYTS Insider;  
\- HOYTS Junior;  
\- HOYTS mobile application;  
\- HOYTS Corporate Solutions;  
\- HOYTS giftstore; and  
\- such other services we may nominate as covered by this Privacy Policy from time to time,

(collectively, **the HOYTS Services** ).

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page.  The revised Privacy Policy will take effect when it is posted on our website.

We refer throughout this Privacy Policy to ‘personal information’ which means information which identifies you as an individual or from which you can reasonably be identified.  Your name, email, address, telephone numbers are all examples of ‘personal information’.

 **Your personal information is important to us**

We are subject to the requirements of the _Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)_. 

We respect the importance of your privacy, and that you have a right to make your own choices about how your personal information is collected and used. We know that when you provide personal information to us you are showing your trust and we take that seriously.

You have no obligation to provide any information requested by us.  However, if you choose to withhold your personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the services or products that depend on the collection and use of that information.

 **How and what personal information do we collect**

We collect your personal information for the HOYTS Services in a number of ways, including:

\- directly from you through our website purchases, loyalty sign-up, sign-up on the HOYTS Rewards and Insider programmes, HOYTS Rewards, HOYTS mobile application and telephone conversations and email correspondence;  
\-  from third parties including our partners, suppliers and public authorities.

The types of personal information we collect includes:

\- your email address, name, address, date of birth and what movies you prefer;  
\- information about your use of our products and services in order to customise our service and make them as interesting as possible for you.

 **The purposes for which we collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information**

 _(a) Primary purpose for collecting your personal information ****_Our purpose in collecting this information is to assist us to provide product and service information tailored to your interests and to provide you with a customised experience across the whole range of HOYTS Services.

 _(b) Use and disclosure of your personal information ****_We will use or disclose your personal information for our primary purpose of providing you product and service information tailored to your interests and to provide you with a customised experience across the whole range of HOYTS Services.

We may also use your personal information to send you marketing information and advertisements about products and services which we think are likely to be of interest to you. If you wish to opt out of receiving any further marketing or advertising material from us, please email us at http://www.hoyts.com.au/guest_service/contact_us.aspx, or, for electronic messages, click “unsubscribe” at the bottom of the messages we send you. 

From time to time, HOYTS conducts competition on its website.  When we run these competitions, we may also give you the choice of being on a mailing list to receive further contact from us.  Unless you choose to receive further communications from HOYTS, the information we collect from your entry in the competition is not used for any purposes other than for the competition. 

 _(c) To whom do we disclose your personal information? ****_We provide your personal information to a third party marketing company which aggregates and de-identifies the information and provide us with report that assist us in marketing the HOYTS Services.  We share these transactional information reports with advertisers to ensure only relevant advertisements are provided to you.

We may also share your personal information with a service partner (such as auditors, lawyers, couriers, computer security companies and hosting services) or a company or person related to us, for example, a related body corporate, a common shareholder or someone with whom we share some common commercial interest. To the extent that these service partners, companies or persons are located in Australia and we give them access to your personal information, they are subject to privacy legislation which prevents them from using the information for any other purposes.

We may also disclose your personal information to our overseas  service providers which have servers located in Sweden and the United States of America. We require the overseas service provider to handle your personal information in accordance with Australian privacy principles. We remain committed to safeguarding your personal information.  
 **  
**We will not otherwise use, disclose or share your personal information with a third party without your consent, unless:

\- required by the law;  
\- we believe on reasonable grounds that disclosure is required to prevent or lessen significant risk to the life or physical, mental or emotional health of the consumer or another person;  
\- we take appropriate action in relation to a reasonable suspicion of unlawful activity, or misconduct of a serious nature, that relates to our functions or activities;  
\- disclosure is required to assist any entity, body or person to locate a person who has been reported as missing;  
\- disclosure is made for the purpose of establishing, exercising or defending a legal or equitable claim; or  
\- disclosure is made for the purposes of a confidential alternative dispute resolution process.

 **Our use of cookies on our website**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. HOYTS uses cookies to make your use of our website and services as convenient as possible, such as by customising your web browser's access so that if you are a HOYTS Rewards member, you can instantly see the current showings at your favourite HOYTS cinemas when you visit our site. Cookies also enable us to offer products and services that can be bought on line.

We use Google Analytics (including Google Remarketing) which uses both first party and third-party cookies to record standard internet traffic information such as when, and how many times, you have visited our site.  We and some third parties (including Google) also use the information from the cookies to optimize ad selection for groups of individuals based on age, gender, interests and past visits to our site.  The cookies also allow us and other third parties to evaluate your interactions with ad services on our site. We have enabled Google Analytics for Display Advertising which allows Google and other third parties to advertise to you on our site, you can opt out of this feature through Google Ads Settings.

Importantly, we do not combine the anonymous information collected through Google Analytics with personally identifiable information.

If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. However, this will mean you will not be able to take full advantage of HOYTS' Services. For example, we will not be able to personalise your website each time you visit.

 **You can access and correct the personal information we keep about you**

If at any time you want to know exactly what personal information we hold about you, you are welcome to access your record by visiting your HOYTS Rewards page on our website. To correct personal information that is inaccurate or out-of-date, please visit HOYTS.com.au and change your registration information accordingly.  

Alternatively, you can access or correct your personal information by contacting us using the ‘Contact Details’ set out below.  Please provide us with as much detail as you can about the particular information you wish to access or correct, in order to help us retrieve it.  We may charge you an access fee to cover our costs of providing that information to you.  We will inform you of applicable fees before they are incurred.

In certain circumstances, such as where there is a criminal inquiry, we may refuse your request to access, or correct, your personal information.  If that is the case, we will provide you with reasons for that decision unless it is unreasonable to do so.

We take reasonable steps to make sure that personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and relevant.

If you wish to delete the personal information we hold about you, please let us know by changing your registration information for  HOYTS Rewards on the website, or by contacting us using the ‘Contact Details’ set out below and we will take reasonable steps to delete the information, unless we need to keep it for legal reasons.

 **Storage and security of your personal information** We take all reasonable steps to protect all of the personal information we hold from misuse, interference and loss, and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. For example, access to your personal information is restricted within HOYTS to employees who have specific authorisation to access such information.

We continually endeavour to improve our security safeguards. However, no data transmission over the internet is guaranteed to be perfectly secure, so we cannot absolutely promise that the information you provide to us using the internet will always be totally secure.

 **Links to other websites** We provides links to websites that are owned and/or operated by third parties. The linked websites are not under our control, and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to our website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of those websites.

 **Our mobile application** We have partnered with InMobi Pte Ltd (InMobi), an independent ad network, to send you advertisements about products and services which we think are likely to be of interest to you through our mobile application. 

In order to ensure advertisements are tailored to you, InMobi may collect device-related and advertising information, for example your device type and the geo-location of your device when you request an advertisement.  InMobi receives device identifier information and the location of the ad request in an anonymised format using one-way hashing and encryption.  InMobi does not store personal information about the user. For more information on the types of information InMobi collects through our mobile application, please visit their privacy policy at <http://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy/>.

InMobi may share anonymised data with us regarding your use of the our mobile application to assist us in sending you relevant advertisements.

By using our application, you consent to InMobi collecting (and us providing to them) device-related and advertising information through our mobile application.  If you do not wish InMobi to collect your device-related and advertising information, you can do so by discontinuing your use of our mobile application or by going to the InMobi Opt Out page at: <http://www.inmobi.com/page/opt-out>.

 **Anonymous transactions**

We will not make it mandatory for visitors to our websites to provide Personal Information unless such information is needed to provide you with a service such as HOYTS Rewards.

We provide you with the option of transacting with us on anonymous basis or through a pseudonym where it is lawful and practicable to do so.  

 **What to do if you wish to make a complaint or have a query**

If you wish to make a complaint about the way in which we handle your personal information, or would like to access or correct your personal information,  please write to Customer Service, The HOYTS Corporation Pty Ltd, PO Box 110 Sydney NSW 2001 or contact us at <http://www.hoyts.com.au/guest_service/contact_us>.

We endeavour to respond to complaints within 14 days of their receipt.  If you are dissatisfied with our response, you may refer the matter to the Australian Information (Privacy) Commissioner (see [www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/)).
